I think now for Rapsida, it's really just a story of step-by-step continuing to drive
up the access environment.
I mean, we see strong demand, very strong demand in the dermatology segment.
We're working on building stronger demand as well in the allergy segment.
In general, once physicians start using the medicine and they get the feedback from the
patients that they're seeing disease.
And so, you know, I think that there's a lot of improvement within, within hours and certainly
within a week that gives a very compelling case to continued use.
But we're trying to stay really disciplined on the gross to net here.
We just believe that if we play the long run out here, remibrutinib has the potential
to be used in a broad range of indications, as you all well know, and any points we give
now, we won't be able to get back in the future.
And so we're just being very thoughtful.
So I think the access will improve.
We'll improve sequentially over the course of this year.
But that will ultimately set us up, I think, for a strong 2027 and then a strong longer
term outlook for remibrutinib in the future.
Thank you.
I will now hand the call back to you, Vas.
Absolutely.
And I just wanted to come back to Richard Vosser's question.
We can confirm that the PCSK9 use was just modestly increased versus the 11% from the
baseline population.
So.
That is not a significant factor we would expect in the studies.
But thanks for that question, Richard.
So thanks, everyone, for joining today's conference call.
So we'll look forward to keeping you up to speed as we have the readouts over the coming
months and, of course, catching up with you in various settings in the meantime.
And we look forward to a strong second half and wish you all a great summer break as well.
Thank you.